You will subscribe to Vijay and you are watching
this incident YouTube channel Friends,
in today's video I am going to tell you
how you can get your two-wheeler claim easily.
If you want to know how to get it, then
you
can watch the second video. Please send it to me on four-wheeler.
In this video I am only going to give you
information about two-wheeler claims.
Friends, this will be the steps that you will have to follow to get the
right claim in the right way. Whether it is
necessary for you to give a claim or
not, when should you not take a claim,
we will also talk about all those things step by step. The
whole process will be there, so let's
talk about the first step. First of all, it will be
here. First of all, you will have to hit your car.
Yes, first of all,
wherever your car collides, in any way,
your car is parked, someone else has come and hit it, whether
you were driving or someone else was driving, then
after all this, whatever
accident has happened, whatever has happened in Pandey,
you should only take photos and videos there,
if you are in a condition to take them then do not take them.  If you are finding that
there was some problem, there was a
traffic jam or you
were not in that condition, then there is no problem for you,
but if you can take it, then take it,
it will be better to show you.
After that, what do you have to do if you are
not able to take it there later, for example, if you park
your car on the side way, then definitely
take a photo of it.
If you do something forcefully yourself
or you have forcibly taken a photo of it, if your car has become old
or is slightly descriptive and
you have added too much to get a
claim that your entire picture should be
changed, then this would be a very wrong thing, you will
not get the deletion at all, you will have to
spend a lot to get it repaired
later, after that you do
not need to worry at all, suppose
you have taken a car in Delhi, it is a Delhi
car and you go to Mumbai by
car and your car meets with an accident there, then there is a
problem like this that you will not get clearance there,
how will you take your
car, wherever there is an accident, then whatever
you  You
can go to any dealership nearby and
your car will be
inspected there. So if your car is in
very bad condition, not in driving condition,
completely broken, and if you drive it, everything will get
damaged, or you are not in driving condition, the vehicle is completely
broken, then what should you do? At
that time, your car is not working properly, and in
such a situation, you have to call them, they will
come with their truck loader and put the car in it and
you will be taken care of. One more thing to keep in mind here is that
any kind of accessories installed in the car,
whether it is a light, an external
phone show, or you have installed a separate legguard, a
stand, or something else, all
those accessories,
minerals, etc., do
not come into play at all. If you are a gender
accident victim, you will get the claim easily,
you do not need to worry, there is
a chance
that someone will reject you, but you have to
talk to them again in a little while,
after that you will get the opportunity to participate. There is no
need to worry at all,
you should have a cool mind.  The entire situation has to be
handled, the vehicle has reached half the dealership
easily, you have taken care of the dealership there
and explained to it how
your Jain has met with an accident
and many parties there are there,
this crush has to be put, so
Muslims do not come to the fort, those who have done the rituals, their wheels are
broken or their direction has changed completely, that
party comes in with the claim, their wheels will be
completely replaced, if there is minor damage or
minor injury, then
you should leave it there, a
little bit is fine,
otherwise you can get a vinyl wrap done on it,
if there is too much grease on the vehicle, then
you can put a dot on that part,
in any colour that is a very good option,
you can put a sticker, so
you have options in that way, but even then you have to get
this part changed, so when the damage is too much, then the
company will also recommend that if there are too many injuries, then
you take the claim, then
what will happen, you will have to sign a paper,
which is the insurance papers of the claim, which is
here  Some
documents will be required like Aadhar card,
PAN card, your license in whose name the
vehicle is, RC of the vehicle and a copy of the insurance.
All these things will be required. After that, a
form will be generated which they will fill themselves and
you will have to sign it. Then your vehicle will be checked to see
which parts
match the specifications and if those are
available at the dealership then the process will become
very simple but right now this is
not available then those points will be put on order first. The
surveyor will come and will
thoroughly check your vehicle to see
which parts you need to replace as
you have just seen them. He will
take the vehicle as per his requirement that it should be replaced and what is
worth replacing which our company can take care of, then
whichever part it finds
suitable, that part will be kept under the claim. The
company will replace it there
and put it in the same part. Then what will happen is that the
dealer
will dismantle the entire vehicle, not the entire vehicle, I mean
that area. If your entire vehicle is damaged then the
entire details will have to be checked, the
entire vehicle will have to be opened because
if there is any damage inside then that too  It comes
inside the company itself, it comes inside the same,
so the car will be opened in this manner and
those officers will take its photo, all those
surveyors will do the
work of
taking the entire photo, the broken parts will be taken
out and their photo will be taken, their
photo will be sent that yes, these parts which have come out
broken, nothing happens to those parts, they
go in this order, after that the
photo of the new parts will be taken by installing them
and then after that the end dealer will
make a complete bill for him, whatever is
fitted in it, the insurance
company will pay it to the company, what we have to do, we do it
here after that, first of all if we
talk about the bike, it depends,
but which insurance of which company and what
things have you taken under the insurance, this is third party
insurance, first party
insurance is one, as is clear from the name itself, third
party means that you go and hit someone else's car, that
means if there is an
accident and you have damaged someone else's car, then
that too will be covered
by your insurance, that car
After that now the third party is
absolutely necessary, without it you
cannot drive a watch, you can drive on the road with third party
verification, it is
very important to have both of these according to me, so the
third party is for 5 years
which has been made mandatory on all bikes
by the government and the third party is for 1 year
which the dealership gives you along with the
one year warranty, if you
want to get more than that while buying the car then
you can get it done, in the middle of all these processes
you can be fooled a lot, whether
by the insurance company
or by the dealer while taking the loan, so you have to be very cautious,
what thing I don't know,
this will become a very long thing, if I will
include this thing in this video, then I will
make a separate proper video for this,
if you want a video in it then
tell me in the comment box below, I will
upload this video soon, what thing do
you have to mix, you are taking, now
one more thing gets added in this, after third party
and third party, whether you have taken zero
depression or not,
which you also call 0f insurance, this
product, then he has  I have taken it, no,
what happens in it, how old is your car, it is
6 months old, one month old or it is
5-6 years old, your
hundred percent, whatever is the new version of the car, the
company will pay hundred percent of that, so it was
something like this,
but if it is not in production and your
car is a little old, then in that, 90%,
80%, whatever will be the price of the car, whatever will be the
condition of the car in which the policy is old, that much will be
paid according to that, the
remaining ten percent to sixty five
percent, whatever is left, you will have to pay,
as it will be your company, there is a
file charge for it, it is normal in bikes,
normally in companies it is 30 or
around that, three hundred and fifty, something like this is there
in the file charge, you have to pay it there,
after that whatever netbots will be required,
taps will be required, it will take some time, some sticker will be required,
you will have to pay for that separately, ₹10,
₹5, whatever it is, they will pay it on their head, let's say
this three hundred and fifty rupees is
yours here  There is a claim there is a profile charge,
after that you get 2 hips and stuff
loaded on top, then you will have to pay around Rs. 500 or Rs. 550,
while picking up the vehicle, all you readers should check it once,
drive the vehicle and see, after that whatever you do
there, it will be proper
that your
doors have been changed in it and you should mix one more
thing and check a little,
if you can go, the doors are being changed, then if
you can go, then I would
say definitely go, you should see your vehicle entering
and how they are
handling it because they are doing it correctly, you should
not fill it in a wrong way, you will fill all
your stuff in it and on top of that they will put all your
parts, then you should check once
that the boring etc. is proper, everything is proper, then you
can go back home, it will be very
good for you, then your
vehicle is completely ready there, you have
lowered it, after that what you have to do is to
pick up the vehicle and go home with sweets,
I am such an assistant professor, if
you like this video, please
like and share this video  If you decide to subscribe to the channel, you will get to
see the Atal program. In this context, you have to
click on a small
circle next to it, click on it. My channel
is subscribed and you will be able to show your support. If you have
any questions or suggestions, you
can tell us in the comment box below. I will meet
you in the next video. When will the reflex be and
that too? Happy
yes,
what happened?